vectorcardservices.com 2014-10-24

# Vector Card Services

This Privacy Policy explains the privacy policies of Vector Card Services (Vector) with respect to the Prepaid Card programs and services provided by Vector. 

We are committed to protecting your privacy and security while offering you our products and services.

This disclosure explains what information we collect about you, and how we use, share and safeguard information in connection with any prepaid card product managed by Vector Card Services. 

**DEFINITIONS**

**We, our, and us,** means Vector Card Services. 

**You, and your,** means consumers who have a prepaid card issued by the issuing partner as displayed on the back of the card and provided by Vector Card Services. This Privacy Policy will apply to you if you are a current or former consumer who has a continuing relationship with us.

**INFORMATION**

**Information we may collect and disclose** includes public and non-public personal information such as your name, address, date of birth, social security number, passport number, driver’s license number, government issued ID, phone number, and email address. This information is collected and maintained to provide you with the financial products or desired services you have requested, to service your accounts and to fulfil legal and regulatory requirements. Non-public personal information is a legal term for information which can identify you and includes personal and financial information which is generally not available to the public. 

We get this type of information from various sources, including information you provide to us during the application process or on other forms, or from government regulatory agencies or consumer reporting agencies which are used to verify your identity.

**Information we may share** as permitted by law may include the information described above. This also may include information regarding your account balance, transaction history, and dispute or claim requests. We permit access to non-public personal information about you only to those persons who need to know that information in order to provide products or services to you. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to guard your non-public personal information. We will comply with more restrictive state laws to the extent that they apply to us.

**ACCESS OR CORRECT YOUR INFORMATION**

You can access some of your information collected and maintained by us at _[www.vectorcardservices.com](http://www.vectorcardservices.com/)_. 

You can correct errors in your information either via the website or by contacting us at support@vectorcardservices.com

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY DISCLOSURE**

**We may change our Privacy Disclosure** from time to time. We will provide current customers with a revised disclosure posted on our website that describes the new practices as required by law. This policy replaces any other previous Privacy Policy about our consumer information sharing practices.

Revised: 04/2013
